<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Vim on jsj&#39;s notebook</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/vim/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Vim on jsj&#39;s notebook</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2021 13:07:21 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/vim/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Creating Vim binding for checkbox using regex for lua configuration</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/vim_checkbox_lua/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2021 13:07:21 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/vim_checkbox_lua/</guid>
      <description>So I have todo list in my vim notes and I wanted to create vim bindings to create checkbox ,close checkbox,open checkbox.I found a article by marcelfischer which had a similar requirement.He had used regex to do so.I decided to do the same for my lua configuration.&#xA;Requirement If there is item with * then we need to add a checkbox&#xA;* todo item 1 * will change into&#xA;* [ ]todo item 1 * [ ] If there is checkbox we should be able to close the same</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vim folding to arrange NeoVim config file</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/vim_folding/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jul 2021 16:09:06 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/vim_folding/</guid>
      <description>Folding in vim I have started using NeoVim as my editor.So I have added lot of configurations in my init.vim file.I keep updating the same when I find some new requirements. So I wanted to manage all the configurations related to NeoVim and its Plugins. I checked various ways and found that folding was one of the methods to do that.Folding is a way of collapsing a group of lines into a single line.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Setup Vim as a Flutter IDE using coc-nvim on windows</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/vim_flutter_ide/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jun 2021 15:41:34 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/vim_flutter_ide/</guid>
      <description>I recently started using Neovim as my text editor.Also right now I am learning Flutter to create a mobile application for my personal project. So I decided to setup Neovim as a Flutter IDE.With this I can practice Vim with Flutter.&#xA;Install Plugins To setup Neovim as Flutter IDE we need to use coc.nvim plugin .Also for formatting, I am using the dart_vim_plugin.We also need the snippets to be loaded like the ones for stateless/stateful widget.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Install Neovim on Windows</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/neovim_install/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jun 2021 13:10:20 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/neovim_install/</guid>
      <description>I had wanted to use vim as my editor for a long time.So in the lockdown time I gave it a try.I installed NeoVim on windows.Below are the steps for that&#xA;Install Neovim using chocolatey So I use chocolatey package manager for installing different software on windows.I installed the Neovim also using chocolatey with the below command. Ensure you use the terminal with Run as administrator.&#xA;choco install neovim Setting up init.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
